(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 20]
♪ Honor and disgrace;
rumors and prejudice ♪
♪ Everyone has their own take ♪
♪ Fingers coated in blood
and disasters brought about ♪
If you're not going to make a move,
♪ Were never what I wanted ♪
I'm leaving.
♪ The great way is fading away,
besieged by mysterious traps ♪
♪ Who dares to treat life and death
as nothing? ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye, the body
collapses, and the soul is destroyed ♪
♪ The fire starts raging across the land ♪
♪ What do you think is ♪
♪ The most impressive farewell
in the world? ♪
♪ The endless slaughter and massacres ♪
♪ Do not wait until that thin snow
on the eaves ♪
♪ Turns a young man's hair white
before you regret it ♪
♪ When do you think ♪
♪ The bloody strife will come to an end? ♪
♪ Burn myself to prove it
without looking back ♪
♪ Holding the morning glow in hand,
I paint the world ♪
♪ The dawn light
illuminates the vast sky ♪
♪ Honor and disgrace;
rumors and prejudice ♪
♪ Everyone has their own take ♪
♪ Fingers coated in blood
and disasters brought about ♪
♪ Were never what I wanted ♪
♪ The great way is fading away,
besieged by mysterious traps ♪
♪ Who dares to treat life and death
as nothing? ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye, the body
collapses, and the soul is destroyed ♪
♪ The fire starts raging across the land ♪
♪ What do you think is ♪
♪ The most impressive farewell
in the world? ♪
♪ The endless slaughter and massacres ♪
♪ Do not wait until that thin snow
on the eaves ♪
♪ Turns a young man's hair white
before you regret it ♪
♪ When do you think ♪
♪ The bloody strife will come to an end? ♪
♪ End these everlasting battles ♪
♪ Holding the morning glow in hand,
I paint the world ♪
♪ Someone's got to clean up this mess ♪
Don't come any closer.
Senior!
Senior, where are you?
Sheng.
Senior.
Sheng!
Senior!
Senior.
No!
No...
Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer!
No!
Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer...
Don't come any closer!
Everyone in the back, keep up.
Hurry up!
Coming.
Senior.
This is bad.
The Young Sect Master has been taken!
Senior Jiang,
please save the Young Sect Master.
Who took him?
Someone from Chongling Valley.
He claimed to be Su Taiyi's Master.
He looked quite young.
We couldn't tell his actual age.
Su Taiyi's master.
is just a physician.
What kind of cultivation could he have?
Lin Muhan
is a cultivator
at the peak of Foundation Establishment.
His father also
equipped him with magical artifacts.
Even someone at the Golden Core Stage
is no challenge for him.
How did he get captured?
His power is unfathomable.
At Chongling Valley,
he struck Mr. Bai Yun down
with a single palm,
and injured Cang Fengzi.
Bai Zongying from Tianyuan Sect
stood by and didn't dare make a sound.
With the Young Sect Master's skills,
it's normal that he was captured.
How did Lin Muhan
provoke this formidable enemy?
He didn't exactly provoke him.
Actually,
they are somewhat friends.
The situation was too chaotic that day.
We were fighting the demonic cultivators
from the Wushuang Society,
and he was fighting
the people from Qinghong Sect.
Later, he was losing,
and the Young Sect Master
couldn't bear to watch it,
so he helped him out a bit.
He helped him,
but still got captured?
Yes.
And then,
the big guy from Qinghong Sect died,
and the rest fled.
As the Young Sect Master
was capturing those demonic cultivators,
he was suddenly grabbed and taken away.
Before leaving,
he left a message.
What message?
"If any of you dare make a move,
I will kill your Young Sect Master."
He is protecting
Wushuang Society's members.
How did Chongling Valley
and Wushuang Society
end up helping each other?
I don't know about that either.
But isn't it normal
for members of Chongling Valley
and Wushuang Society
to help each other?
Just look at
his attitude towards ordinary mortals
and his attitude
towards us in the immortal sect.
Senior Jiang,
what should we do now?
What do you mean?
The Young Sect Master has been captured.
We must save him.
Isn't that your business?
Mine?
I came here on my master's orders
to capture the people of Wushuang Society.
I don't care about anything else.
Nangong Guhong and I
will continue forward
to Phoenix City.
That is the ultimate goal
of Wushuang Society.
Take your people and go.
Go and save Lin Muhan.
Who's there?
Don't run!
Xin.
They ate my leg.
They ate my leg!
Kill me!
Quick, kill me!
Yes.
The War Demons
are all evil.
You're a disciple of the immortal sect.
I am a remnant of the War Demons.
It's only natural
that you want to kill me.
Go find Sheng.
Tell her not to take risks
and come back as soon as possible.
Don't take risks,
come back as soon as possible.
Tell her,
I am worried about her.
Worried about her.
[Phoenix City]
Come, Lu.
It's time to eat.
Lu.
Lu?
Have your injuries
worsened again?
Right,
I have
the last two Yangyuan Pills here.
Eat them.
You'll have strength after that.
No need.
What day is it today?
Today?
July 15th.
Oh yeah,
it's the Ghost Festival.
Later,
leave the city from the west gate
and keep walking south.
You'll reach the inn we came from.
Are we going back?
You are going back by yourself.
You brought me here,
and now you want me to leave?
I'm not leaving.
Here comes the sheep blood tofu stew.
Let's eat.
Enjoy your meal, gentlemen.
Lu,
you must try this.
The sheep blood tofu stew
is a North Xiang specialty.
Phoenix City makes the
most authentic ones.
They use fresh sheep blood.
By the way,
I took a peek in the backyard.
They're using young lambs.
Very tender.
Why isn't it cooked?
Attendant!
The sheep blood isn't fully cooked!
Come here and take a look.
Attendant!
Hurry up and get me a cooked one.
I am so sorry.
I will get you a new one right away.
I will get you a new one.
Where is he?
Qianqiao,
your Bloodthirst is acting up.
Mother...
Go kill him.
Then you won't feel so miserable.
You killing them
is like them
slaughtering a chicken
or a dog at will.
Cats catch mice,
and humans eat meat.
It's the law of nature.
And we
were born to eat them.
Do it.
Drain their blood,
and you'll be free.
No.
No!
Do it.
Do it!
You again.
I was just wondering
where to find you for my revenge.
And here you've found me yourself.
Jiang Ji,
aren't you going to stab her?
After that day,
I tossed and turned every night,
worried that Senior Jin Lun
had struck too hard
and finished you off,
giving you a quick death.
Fortunately,
you didn't let me down.
You think reaching the Golden Core Stage
is enough to catch me?
I'm not stopping there.
Not only will I catch you,
but I will also lock you up,
torture you every day,
and make you wish you were dead.
It's you.
Do you know her?
She's a disciple of Xin Xie Manor.
Sheng, I think.
Before, in Chongling Valley,
I met her senior,
and almost got into a fight
with Bai Zongying's people.
This is my senior.
She left the mountain for errands
and hasn't returned for a long time.
You know her,
don't you?
What's her senior's name?
Xin Mei.
Still won't admit defeat?
As long as I'm not dead,
I have not lost.
I see.
I didn't expect a mere Xin Xie Manor
to stir up
such a huge wave.
Stop.
Madam Wu.
There is a girl here.
[Madam Wu]
She looks decent
and has a good figure.
Let's take her back.
Yes.
Here.
Boss, this way please.
The work this time isn't that heavy.
Once it's done,
we'll take a good rest.
Sure.
When we get into the city,
we'll find a good restaurant
and have a good drink.
That's great.
Here.
Okay.
I'll treat you then.
Sure.
When did you arrive?
A few days ago.
What took you guys so long?
We got new information
right before we set off.
Those demonic cultivators
split into 3 groups
while heading for Phoenix City.
So we had no choice but to
split into 3 groups to go after them.
Senior Bai led the Tianyuan Sect,
Jiang Ji and I moved together,
and Lin Muhan went alone.
Lin Muhan went alone?
You were supposed to go with him,
but your Master said
you had already hit the road.
So we made a temporary arrangement
for him to go alone.
We don't expect him to succeed anyway.
It doesn't matter.
We have already succeeded
and eliminated
all the demonic cultivators.
Senior Bai's side
probably won't have any problems either.
Didn't they say
it was enough to capture them?
You killed them all?
Wushuang Society
is not to be trifled with.
They had experts, too.
Capturing them
was not an easy task.
What's more,
they were all demonic cultivators.
It's not a pity
killing them at all.
One more thing.
The female cultivator in the capital
is Xin Mei.
How do you know?
We met that woman again.
Who?
The one who stopped
Nangong and me on our way here.
She is also a disciple of Xin Xie Manor,
named Sheng.
The senior she was looking for before
was Xin Mei.
You fought her?
Yes.
How is she?
I mean,
she is quite skilled
and has high cultivation.
Are you guys okay?
We are fine.
Last time, she played some tricks.
This time, we met head-on.
Jiang Ji's cultivation has improved too.
She had no chance to hurt her.
I am already at the Golden Core Stage.
So you captured her?
Where did you put her?
You killed her?
Yes.
Just as she was about to escape,
Jiang Ji struck her
with her sword from afar.
But we didn't find
her body either.
Your sword pierced her chest.
In this vast desert,
where could she
possibly escape to?
She won't live long.
Sheng.
Sheng!
Sh...
♪ I accept the blame of
numerous accusations ♪
♪ I offer no defense ♪
♪ To protect what I believe is worth it ♪
Sheng. Sheng!
Wake up.
Sheng!
♪ I admit my heart
is as hard as iron and stone ♪
♪ Call me cold if you must ♪
♪ I'll risk it all ♪
Sheng. Sheng!
Let's go.
[Phoenix City]
Are you feeling better?
Why did you come to North Xiang?
It's the Ghost Festival.
I was afraid your Bloodthirst
would act up
and put you in danger.
What time is it?
It's past 9 p.m.
Your Bloodthirst
flares up
every year during the Ghost Festival.
But this time,
it's far worse than before.
The more unstable your state of mind is,
the harder it is to control yourself.
Lu.
You need to rest for a while.
Don't fight with anyone anymore.
Not yet.
The young man after Xin Mei
is a cultivator at the Void Stage.
He is quite powerful.
I can't figure out his background,
which makes me feel uneasy.
As for the Qinghong Sect,
another of their Dharma Kings is dead.
We have no idea
who they will blame for this.
I haven't been gone for long,
yet so much has happened.
Xin Mei
found out about my identity.
So you had a fight?
You knew?
I guessed it.
While you were passed out,
you kept mumbling something
about Xin Mei
and War Demons.
Tell me about it.
How did she treat you?
Did she try to kill you?
There's nothing to talk about.
War Demons and the Human Race
have a deep-seated hatred for each other.
Anyone who found out my identity
would react the same way.
No matter what,
these things started because of me,
so the responsibility is mine.
I can't just sit by and do nothing.
I really should let her see
how warm-hearted you are right now.
You don't look like
a War Demon at all.
When do we leave?
Tomorrow.
Big bets, big payouts;
small bets, small payouts.
Roll the dice! Roll the dice!
Place your bets! Hurry up!
Big bets, big payouts;
small bets, small payouts.
Big! Big! Big!
[Sha Sanxing]
All bets are final.
Big! Big! Big!
Reveal.
Small.
Again, again!
I lost again.
You plan to look for Sha Sanxing,
that lackey?
Let me tell you,
he has a bad character.
Don't associate yourself with him.
Another round.
Keep betting. Come on.
Come on, bet.
Bet on big. Big!
I'll bet on big.
Big! Big! Big!
Come on, bet on big. Big!
Why are you running?
For a moment,
I didn't know why,
but my legs wouldn't listen to me.
I swear.
After you left,
I didn't commit any
arson, murder, or theft.
I'm a law-abiding citizen now,
doing my part.
I just have a little hobby
I haven't quit yet.
I'll turn into a dog if I lie to you.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Have a seat.
I want to ask you about someone.
Who?
I don't know his name.
He looks like a young cultivator.
He has black hair,
a red mole between his eyebrows,
doesn't dress like someone
from the Central Plains,
and has good cultivation techniques.
Lately,
he should be at the Void Stage.
Absolutely not.
I just suddenly remembered that
I have to confess something to you.
What is it?
Two years ago,
before I got addicted to gambling,
I had a lover
in the brothel.
What a coincidence.
The person you are looking for
is related to my lover.
Two years ago,
someone gave my lover
a sum of money
to have a child for him.
Then,
she left with him for less than 2 months
and came back pregnant.
When she came back,
she kept muttering to me,
saying she got a great deal.
She said the one who asked for help
was a cultivator.
He was a handsome young man,
generous
and gentle to her.
She stayed at his house for 2 months.
It was wonderful for her.
Back then, she told me that
the cultivator had
a cinnabar mole between his eyebrows.
Where is
this lady now?
She died long ago.
Bled to death giving birth.
What about the child?
I saw her a few times before she left.
Her belly
was huge.
She said she was carrying a boy.
I was very curious then.
How did she know it was a boy
before the child was even born?
Anyway, she was in bad shape.
She was thin and weak.
She passed away
right after giving birth.
And strangely enough,
when the child was born,
it really was a boy.
Where is the child?
I don't know about that.
He was taken away
by the man you mentioned.
But I just thought of someone.
Maybe she'd know.
Do you know the best dancer
in North Xiang,
Yaoniang?
Don't get me wrong.
My lover used to be
friends with Yaoniang.
They were close to each other.
Go ask her.
She definitely knows more than I do.
Where is she?
Tianxiang Restaurant.
[Tianxiang Restaurant]
Excuse me.
Call the manager here.
I have some questions.
Sir,
are you here for Yaoniang?
You are smart, Miss.
Then I can't help you
with this favor.
Look.
All the gentlemen in this building
are here for Yaoniang.
Everyone is offering money
to see her ahead of others.
But Yaoniang can't receive
so many people.
Please wait a little longer.
If you feel bored,
you can find other girls
to drink wine with you.
I just want to ask a few questions.
How long do I have to wait?
Looking at this situation,
you'd be lucky to see her by the
first watch, and speak to her
by the third.
Friend,
is this your first time
at Tianxiang Restaurant?
Please enlighten me.
Yaoniang is Tianxiang Restaurant's
most famous dancer.
Her Huxuan dance
is famous all over North Xiang.
Although she is from a brothel,
she is pure
and never sells her body.
Half a year ago,
Lord Qian, the magistrate of Phoenix City,
took a fancy to her.
Lord Qian
is already 60 years old.
He has a fierce wife at home,
but still wants to take
Yaoniang as a concubine.
He's using his power to oppress people,
forcibly take a civilian lady,
all to make her a concubine.
How shameless.
But Yaoniang didn't want to.
She said she already had a sweetheart
and would marry him soon.
Lord Qian
didn't want to force her.
He gave Yaoniang half a year.
If she really got married,
he'd let it be.
If not,
she'd have to be his concubine.
Now the 6 months are up,
but Yaoniang is still not married.
We thought
Lord Qian would take her as a concubine
for sure.
Unexpectedly,
Tianxiang Restaurant suddenly announced
a flower-viewing event.
Yaoniang
will be retiring with her new
Luanxue Dance at the event.
See,
the wealthy flower-viewers in the city
are all gathered here
just to catch a glimpse
of the top dancer in North Xiang.
Friend.
If you also like Yaoniang,
you can also make an offer
and join the bidding.
As long as your offer is high,
you will have a chance tonight
to have a good chat with her all night.
Thank you, friend.
Isn't that the boy from Lingji Mountain?
Why is he here too?
What a coincidence.
Keep an eye on her.
Today is Yaoniang's big day.
Don't let her run away or get lost
and cause trouble.
After today,
we can take our time disciplining her.
Rest assured.
If you do well,
you will be rewarded.
Where is my sword?
It's so lively outside,
but we have to guard the door here.
I also want to see Yaoniang's dance.
Enough.
Making you guard here
is not a bad thing.
The young lady inside
has a great figure.
I'm telling you,
Madam Wu values her very much.
She wants to make her
the new top courtesan
after Yaoniang leaves.
You...
Shut up if you don't want to die.
I have a question.
Answer well, and I'll spare your life.
I said I just wanted to
ask you a question.
What are you waiting for?
Are we still
looking for Yaoniang?
What's the matter, Sir?
When Yaoniang appears later,
how should I bid?
Peonies are 50 taels each.
Roses are 20 taels.
The rest are 10 taels each.
Sir, you can exchange money for flowers.
When the ladies appear later,
if you see someone you like,
you can put the flowers
in the basket in front.
The type and number of flowers
represent the bid.
Today, besides Yaoniang,
there are other ladies dancing too.
Sir, you have many choices.
Here.
100 taels is indeed a lot,
but for this occasion,
I'm afraid it won't win the bid.
If you don't want to join the fun, Sir,
100 taels is enough to find someone else.
For example,
me.
I'd be very happy to dance for you,
even for free.
Here.
Thank you, Sir.
I say,
if Su Taiyi knew
the money he left you
was spent like this,
he'd be
rolling in his grave.
Yaoniang.
Why are you still here?
The event is about to start.
Go and prepare.
Yaoniang,
listen to me.
So you finally came.
I thought you were scared
of that old man's authority
and didn't dare come for me.
Yes.
I really was scared then.
But I'm not scared anymore.
I'll take you away.
We'll leave North Xiang,
flee far away,
and never come back.
I didn't see anything.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It's starting.
Yuniang, please go on the stage.
Which one is Yaoniang?
You don't know?
Naturally, I don't know either.
Better to reward the wrong one
than miss the right one.
How about
we hang it up first?
Nice!
So nice.
Such a great dance.
Nice!
So nice.
Absolutely wonderful.
Nice!
This one looks like her.
This one?
Second floor, Chuan Room—Mr. Lu
has bid 500 taels
for a private meeting with Yuniang
to enjoy a graceful dance
beneath the flowers and moonlight!
Nice!
Yuniang?
This isn't Yaoniang.
What should we do?
What else can we do?
Keep hanging rewards.
Why are you here?
Do you know me?
Why do you look so familiar?
Forget it.
That doesn't matter.
Do you drink wine?
Come, let's drink.
Come on.
Drink up.
This trip is totally worth it.
Yeah.
Eat, eat.
Tonight is really worth it.
Nice!
Decisive.
What a beautiful figure.
Cheers.
Yaoniang.
Why are you here drinking?
Come with me, quick.
You are going on stage.
Come on.
Keep drinking.
Where's the lady who was drinking with me?
Sir,
do you want more wine?
No need.
Sir, you act as if
you've never held a lady's hand before.
Why so shy?
Friend.
If you waste your luck with the lady,
you'll be cursed by heaven.
Friend,
your target, Yaoniang, is here.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Everyone here
is after Yaoniang.
You guys are rich and powerful.
I can't compete with you.
So I might as well
let you bid on a few more ladies
and deplete your money.
Friend,
you're using the
Thirty-Six Stratagems here?
That's playing dirty.
Yaoniang,
why aren't you dancing?
Yeah, why not?
Dance, dance, Yaoniang!
Dance!
Sir.
No, thanks.
Hurry up and dance!
Hurry up!